But beforehand, I would prefer to come here and as you see, we have zero credits, so this is not good at all.
This may mean that we cannot use the tool at all.
But the point here is that first, I want to go and see the plans and pricing that it provides us with.
So, how do I do that?
I click here and wait to see if we can do plans and pricing of the tool.
Yes, so as you see, we have photorepro, which we can access for $2.66 per month.
And we have photorepro plus, which we can access for $5.24 per month.
And these are the options that we have, so they are ad-free and they have all these options as you see.
So, I close this one and it says, let's work here.
So, I go to home and this is basically all that we have.
So, about the credits I am concerned because if we need, if you want to learn the tool, you've got to use it.
And if we want to use it, we need credits.
But the point here is that, okay, so let's go ahead to see how it goes.